(electronic dance music)
♪ Take me home ♪
♪ Baby, I know you're wondering ♪
♪ Why I won't go over to your place ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm not too
sure 'bout how you feel ♪
♪ So I'd rather go at my own pace ♪
♪ And I know and you know
that if we get together ♪
♪ Emotions will go to work ♪
♪ And I may do something I
might regret the next day ♪
♪ And end up hurt ♪
♪ Oh, I don't know ♪
♪ That's the way that I
feel (Way that I feel) ♪
♪ I'm so afraid of a one
night deal (I need you, so) ♪
♪ I wonder if I take you home ♪
♪ Would you still be in love, baby? ♪
♪ Because I need you tonight ♪
♪ I wonder if I take you home ♪
♪ Would you still be in love, baby? ♪
♪ Because I need you tonight, huh-ho ♪
♪ Your love is ♪
♪ (Take me home) ♪
♪ Lately, you've been expressing to me ♪
♪ Just how much you want to make love ♪
♪ I want it just as much as you do ♪
♪ But will you still keep in touch ♪
♪ You say I'm teasing,
but I do have a reason ♪
♪ Don't let your feelings fade ♪
♪ 'Cause you will have me
and sooner than you know it ♪
♪ If you could only wait ♪
♪ Oh, I don't know ♪
♪ That's the way that I
feel (Way that I feel) ♪
♪ I'm so afraid of a one night deal, ♪
♪ And sometimes (I'm so afraid) ♪
♪ I wonder if I take you home ♪
♪ Would you still be in love, baby? ♪
♪ Because I need you tonight ♪
♪ I wonder if I take you home ♪
♪ Would you still be in love,
baby? (Home, home, home, home) ♪
♪ Because I need you tonight ♪
♪ I wonder if I take you home ♪
♪ Would you still be in love, baby? ♪
♪ Because I need you tonight ♪
♪ I wonder if I take you home ♪
♪ Would you still be in love,
baby? (Home, home, home, home) ♪
♪ Because I need you tonight, huh-ho ♪
♪ (Oh, I wonder. I
really, really wonder) ♪
♪ (Home, home, home, home) Take me home ♪
♪ (Oh, I wonder. I
really, really wonder) ♪
♪ (Take me home) ♪
♪ Your love is ♪
♪ (Take me, take me, take me home) ♪
♪ (Take me, take me, take me
home) Home, home, home, home ♪
♪ Ooh, na-na-na-na-na ♪
♪ Na-na-na-na-na, no (Home) ♪
♪ You're down on your knees ♪
♪ Begging me, please, huh-ho ♪
♪ (Take me home) Take you home, oh ♪
♪ Will you still love me ♪
♪ If I take you home ♪